<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Freelancing | EZ 2 Hack]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/freelancing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-14T14:42:50+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ong Swee San]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting work as a Freelance developer]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/13/getting-work-as-a-freelance-developer/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-13T12:12:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/13/getting-work-as-a-freelance-developer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How does one go about getting work as a Freelance developer? The number one question I get when I introduce my self as a freelancer is "How to get work?". Most freelancer start out having no idea how to find new clients.</p>

<p>I have mention 4 ways to find work in the previous post:
1. Referral from a friends, family member, Ex-Employees, Ex-Colleagues or just about anyone you knows.
2. Your Website or Blog
3. From online job boards or on a freelance website like Elance, ODesk, or Freelancer.com
4. From online classified ads.
All of the above requires constantly looking, goggling, searching and talking to people. It will probably take up more time then development before you get your first 3 clients. I have the most success getting referrals from ex-colleagues and ex-employers.</p>

<p>Because all these looking and searching for new client may takes time, you will need a remember a few things when you get your client:
1. Keep existing client, generate recurring revenue form them, or at least keep the relationship going.
2. Keep billing organize, bill on time because chasing payments are painful.
3. Ask for referral from existing client.</p>

<p>Be the go to person for your expertise is the eaiuest way to get referral. Put effort in your work, give extra values. If you did a good job that client will tell others and getting new business will be easier.</p>

<p>What I am achieving is to create a lead generation channel, an automated system that constantly bring in and qualifies new clients. I share this in the future posts.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
