<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Freelancing | A Freelance Programmer's Log.]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/freelancing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-27T16:45:14+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ong Swee San]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should you work for equity instead of cash?]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/17/should-you-work-for-equity-instead-of-cash/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-17T10:23:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/17/should-you-work-for-equity-instead-of-cash</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I been asking a few times to take equity instead of cash to help with the development of mostly startups or those who wants to do start up.
I would definitely take equity if a right project I like comes along.</p>

<p>My rules are :
1. If project have good potential and generates income right form the start, I take equity.
2. If project have good potential and may generate income in distant future, I take small equity plus small upfront cash.
3. If project have no potential, I charge full development cost.
4. Reject anything else thats a waste of time.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to use LinkedIn Groups to get more clients ]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/16/how-to-use-linkedin-groups-to-get-more-clients/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-16T10:11:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/16/how-to-use-linkedin-groups-to-get-more-clients</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Most people just waste time on LinkedIn, browsing randomly and sending out odd connection requests hoping to land a jobs. Most of them are looking the wrong way. The secret is in LinkedIn Groups. LinkedIn Groups are a very good way to get more clients for your freelance business. LinkedIn has over 200 million users, most groups have at least a thousand members and you can tap into this crowd to find your target customers. There always people looking to solve a problem. Join groups related to your industries and participate in the problem solving not join random discussion, and soon you be the expert of the group and most people will go directly to you. If you have optimizing your LinkedIn profile according to what you are offfering, you get a steady flow of job offers.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[freelancing 2 years in]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/15/freelancing-2-years-in/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-15T13:02:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/15/freelancing-2-years-in</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This month was my second year as a freelance programmer. This are somethings that have worked well.</p>

<h2>Recurring income</h2>

<p>Always ask for more work from existing client. Charge a monthly for maintenances if you can.</p>

<h2>Tools</h2>

<p>Macbook air, Dell 23 inch have been the best investment ever. I hope to get a new MBA with more ram than the current 4g and a 27i nch Monitor thats now cost less than $500. A mac pro would be ideal but a spec up one is really costly.</p>

<h2>Skills</h2>

<p>C#, PHP and javascript are the most common skill I am using. I write a lot python scripts to process things.</p>

<h2>Networking</h2>

<p>I attended a lot more events and hackathons. I make some really good connections.</p>

<h2>learning</h2>

<p>I learn a lot of marketing techniques since.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a reliable lead generation channel for your freelancing business]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/14/creating-a-reliable-lead-generation-channel-for-your-freelancing-business/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-14T11:02:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/14/creating-a-reliable-lead-generation-channel-for-your-freelancing-business</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When I started freelancing I did not have a constant flow of clients. I search job boards, forums and classified ads, there were not many jobs and it was hard to convert those prospects into clients. I didn't know what to do.</p>

<p>Since then I have gather a few methods from various freelancer and marketers I came across that have work well.</p>

<h2>Define The Types of Client</h2>

<p>For me a good client will be someone for pays $5000 or more for a single project. Loosely translate to $500 per man-day charge. Anything less are just not worth the time and effort even if I have no income. Recurring revenue is another thing that I would focus on. Clients I take on should be coming back to me for more work.</p>

<h2>Lead Source</h2>

<p>Leads can be generated through:
1. On-line classified ads.
This are slow, and may generate 1 or 2 leads per month, but maintenances is easy. Most of the ads run for a month, then you go back and turn it on again. Use Google calender to set reminders, keep the url in the calender, so when an reminder is send, all you need to do is click the url.
2. Blog
It takes a lot effort to get ranked in the search engine. Some SEO knowledge required here
3. PPC Paid Ads
Using Adwords and facebook ads can generate the fastest and most relevant leads.
4. Linkedin
People are always looking for someone good in certain skill set. Setting up a good profile can help generate a fair amount of traffic</p>

<h2>Building the list</h2>

<p>Now you have gather all the source, you need channel them to a place where you can keep build relationships. Use an opt-in list builder like mailchimp. Set up a landing page to catch all that traffic. Set up an series of emails.</p>

<h1>Other more manual generation</h1>

<p>Responding to wanted ads, forum query and user groups and posting links back to your blog post which eventually end up on your landing page.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelancing]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/13/freelancing/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-13T14:22:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/13/freelancing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>More programmers are try their hands at freelancing full-time. They are driven by the dream to be independent and living without a 9-to-5 job constraints. Does a full-time freelancer get to work he you want, take vacations when you want, for as long as he wants. For me its not, I start freelancing 2 years ago, this are somethings I learn along the way. If you're looking to start freelancing and not sure how you can go about it, then read on.</p>

<h2>Motivation</h2>

<p>Decide why you want to freelance. More time for family, more time for health, less commuting, no office politics, no more long boring meetings or the comfort of working from your own home. Knowing your motivation will help will go through tough times and taking full time employment again.</p>

<h2>Finding work</h2>

<p>The one most ask question I get when I introduce my self as a freelancer is "How to get work?". Well, there are a few ways to find work:
1. Referral from a friends, family member, Ex-Employees, Ex-Colleagues or just about anyone you knows.
2. Your Website or Blog
3. From online job boards or on a freelance website like Elance, ODesk, or Freelancer.com
4. From online classified ads.
All of the above requires constantly looking, goggling, searching and talking to people. It will probably take up more time then development before you get your first 3 clients. I have the most success getting referrals from ex-colleagues and ex-employers.</p>

<h2>Whats my rate?</h2>

<p>The next most important thing is how much to charge? Working out how much to charge clients is very difficult. I would recommend you work out you hourly rate. Try this formula if you are having trouble determine you hourly rate. Take your highest monthly pay, divide it by the number of working days, divide the result by 8, then increase it by 20%. You should get a reasonable hourly rate. Remember if you have low rate, you have a hard time trying to raise it later on.</p>

<p>To sum it up, as a freelancer, your next paycheck is never guaranteed. You are always searching for your next project while you chase the payment of the previous one.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
