<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Internet marketing tool | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/internet-marketing-tool/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast is better for Adword targeted landing page]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/06/19/fast-is-better-for-adword-targeted-landing-page/"/>
    <updated>2008-06-19T12:53:03+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/06/19/fast-is-better-for-adword-targeted-landing-page</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Starting today, the time taken to load your landing page will be a factor in Google Adwords keywords' Quality Scores. Google AdWords system will evaluates all targeted landing pages on a regular basis. If you make significant improvements to your landing page's load time, you get a better Quality Score and lower minimum cost-per-click (CPC) bids.</p>

<p>Several affects a web page loading time such as bandwidth, server, web page design. The new rule should benefit small business rather than big corporation who have unlimited adverting budgets. So start optimizing those landing pages.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Adwords]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/06/11/google-adwords/"/>
    <updated>2008-06-11T15:34:33+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/06/11/google-adwords</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://www.perrymarshall.com/google/ultimateguide.jpg" alt="" /></p>

<p>I been reading <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1599180308?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=wizcoder-20&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;creativeASIN=1599180308">"The ultimate guide to google adwords by perry marshall and bryan todd."</a> It's really good, if you are using Google AdWords or are planning to I high recommend you getting this. You get some bonus tools with this tools. A few mp3 which are really good. If you are not familiar with AdWords and think that you can just figure it out, I lost around $300 on AdWords doing that. So getting the book is a lot cheaper. I have to agreed I knew most of the stuff in the book but it really organizing all this knowledge into a system. I have started running a campaign on Yahoo Search Marketing. <a href="http://www.jdoqocy.com/click-2613438-10457500">Sign up and get a $25 credit.</a>. You can get $25 credit for every new account you sign up but you will need a new credit card for each account. I have not set up my new Adword account since I still waiting for new credit card to arrive (I have cancel all my cards previously). The plan is to learn to make $10 a day. After some experiment, I will looking forward to join Perry Marshall's <a href="http://m171.infusionsoft.com/go/mastermind/javaongsan/">AdWords Consultation &amp; Monthly Membership</a>.</p>

<p>For those of you working on keywords for your AdWords , <a href="http://affiliate.wordtracker.com/r/699/a/137624/l/hp4kv6">Wordtracker</a> recently launched a promotion offering new subscribers unlimited 7 day access to the full version for FREE.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
