<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: internet marketing | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/internet-marketing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PPC Tips]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/12/14/ppc-tips/"/>
    <updated>2008-12-14T07:41:27+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/12/14/ppc-tips</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I recently moved to my new place, its good to move out of my parent's place after 35 years. The move took longer than expected about 2 months actually. All this well I have been able to do any actual work on my websites. Most of my website are simply sold as domains. I have been focusing intensely on PPC. I have managed to create profitable campaigns after studying lots of materials from various gurus. I have formatted my own sets of rules.
1. Create a system. Whether its niche research, finding keywords, locating products or setting up campaign. Create a system where you are able to go through the same process again for each new project. You might start with some else system but on the way refine it. Be prepare to throw away what your believes or what you have learn and accept new ideas.
2. Always go deep on keywords. One of the most valuable lesson I have learn is to go deep. People search for phrase when they are seeking solution, they are looking for specific solution so your keyword needs to cater these searches.
3. Measurement. I believe in measuring and keeping scores. Always have tracking codes install. Always check your campaign. Always keep records, create a excel if you have to, to monitor your profits.
4. Never turn off a campaign, searches fluctuates. Whats not popular might be in the future.
5. Out bid your opponent, what PPC was create for, is for business to out bid each other. Most rookie make the mistake of bidding too low. Don't be afraid to bid for keywords that cost more than a dollar.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speed listening]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/09/20/speed-listening/"/>
    <updated>2008-09-20T15:16:12+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/09/20/speed-listening</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Do you learn using audios like mp3s? Here's a tip to double or trible your learning time by speeding up your audio. Download  <a href="http://audacity.sourceforge.net/"><em>Audacity</em></a> it's a Free Audio Editor. Once you installed the software, import the mp3 file you wish to speed up and set the sample rate format higher.
<img src="http://localhost:8888/wizcoder/wp-content/uploads/audacity.jpg" alt="" />
Play the mp3, now you have a faster audio that you can go listen at a shorter time. This method is say to increase your concentration and absorption rate.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can't make money blogging]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/06/you-cant-make-money-blogging/"/>
    <updated>2008-03-06T06:45:46+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/06/you-cant-make-money-blogging</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to popular believe, you can't make lots of money blogging. If you believe that writing a blog will eventually make you a six figure income and quick your job, this is going to hurt. I know you list all the six figure income bloggers and all your endless example to prove me   wrong. If you are one such blogger, I grantee your income is as low as your daily bus fare.</p>

<p>You don't make money blogging, you make money marketing your blog. Make Sense? Income from blogs comes from ad placement. To sell and ad you need to market your blog. No advertiser will know that you have a blog and that you are selling ad space. To promote your blog, you need to do it at forums, other blog, social networking sites and build up your brand. Then you need traffic and readers to boast your revenue, you can't get this by blogging. You get this done by doing  whole lot of other things.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
