<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: contest | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/contest/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Top Commentator Contest Follow up]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/22/blog-top-commentator-contest-follow-up/"/>
    <updated>2008-01-22T06:40:45+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/22/blog-top-commentator-contest-follow-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I am giving away 4 125x125 ad box for the top commentator on my blog for the month of January 2008. The rules are simple, the winner will be the one with the highest accumulated comments till the end of Jan 2008. For the winners your ad will run through the entire month of February.</p>

<p>The current leader is Julia with a whopping 12 comments, follow by Artic (2), alphafoobar (1), Lixena (1), Loreance (1), Michael Kwan (1). There a good chance to win if you put in 2 comments. To post a comment, just click on any post title and you find the comment box below the post. After entering your post click on the word "Post Comment". Remember to include your email.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Top Commentator Contest]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/18/blog-top-commentator-contest/"/>
    <updated>2008-01-18T08:20:46+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/18/blog-top-commentator-contest</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I am giving away 4 125x125 ad box for the top commentator on my blog for the month of January 2008. There are currently no comments for the month of January so I thought I set up a contest to spice things up. The rules are simple, the winner will be the one with the highest accumulated comments till the end of Jan 2008. At the rate, this blog is going, 1 comment will be enough to win yourself a ad box on my sidebar. Your ad will run through the entire month of February I have install the Top Commentator widget, you be able to check your progress there.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
