<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Development | A Freelance Programmer's Log.]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/development/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-27T15:04:41+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ong Swee San]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to control Mdi form Menu dynamically for different login user]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/19/how-to-control-mdi-form-menu-dynamically-for-different-login-user/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-19T08:25:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2014/01/19/how-to-control-mdi-form-menu-dynamically-for-different-login-user</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Controlling winform for multi-user application can be easy achieve by limiting menu access based on login user.
Most of the time, a role is required because many user have the same access rights. We can either add this manually or have everything store in an database.</p>

<pre><code>```

foreach (ToolStripItem item in menuStrip1.Items)
{
    item.Enabled = RoleAccess.IsEnable(RoleId);
    item.Visible = RoleAccess.IsEnable(RoleId);
}

```
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evernote Programming Challenge]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2013/02/27/evernote-programming-challenge/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-27T15:53:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2013/02/27/evernote-programming-challenge</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
Evernote is running a "Evernote Programming Challenge" to recurit engineers. Most of them are based in US. Took the challenge anyway, it was fun. I used python and manage to solve all the problem after a few tries. Not bad for a python newbie.
Check out the challenge at <a href="https://evernotechallenge.interviewstreet.com/challenges">here</a>.
My codes <a href="https://github.com/javaongsan/evernotechallenge">here</a>.

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Windows Phone App]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2012/10/15/my-first-windows-phone-app/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-15T11:37:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2012/10/15/my-first-windows-phone-app</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
    I have been working on windows mobile for the last 10 years starting with VB 3.0 up to .NET. This is the first time I work on a consumer app. I have release an app called Skymusic. I found out that there are already another app named the same way.
</p>


<p>
    I have been using Omina 7 with Windows Phone 7.5. I have found that from time to time I am not able to sync my medias over. I have lots of music I would like to put on my phone. The fatest way would be from a could storage since most of my stuff are there. However there are very few apps that offers download to local from could especially from skydrive. So I build a simple app that could just do that.
    
    The live SDK was not that suitable for a job like this, its does not handles continuos donwload well. It woul be fine if I let select one file at a time for download or may be stream it on demand. I wanted to used wifi and download all the files when I have a fsater connection.
    </p>


<p>
    After 3 or maybe 4 days, my apps was rejected. I had to make some changes using the tips from <a href="http://www.hanselman.com/blog/FromConceptToCodeIn6HoursShippingMyFirstWindowsPhoneApp.aspx">From Concept to Code in 6 hours: Shipping my first Windows Phone App</a>
    
    1. The app keep crashing when in continous download mode, I had to change the design to a click 1 item at time to download. 
    2. Replace my buttons with Coding4Fun Windows Phone Toolkit.
    3. Replace screenshots I capture using print screen with the one I took using <a href="http://www.jeff.wilcox.name/2011/10/screenshots-cs-how-to-capture-screenshots-of-your-app-on-your-device/">screenshots.cs"</a> from the crazy-useful Jeff Wilcox.
    
    Resubmitted the app and it was approved, but I mistakenly select $6.99 for pricing. 
    
    I made a website www.skymusicapp.com using the <a href="http://wp7appsite.codeplex.com/">One-Page Windows Phone 7 App Website Template</a> with <a href="https://github.com/raul/rack-static-boilerplate">rack static boilerplate</a> and hosted it on heroku.
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
