<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: increase web site traffic | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/increase-web-site-traffic/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase website traffic with Trafficswarm]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/09/increase-website-traffic-with-trafficswarm/"/>
    <updated>2008-01-09T10:51:35+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/09/increase-website-traffic-with-trafficswarm</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the constant struggle of webmaster is trying to  increase website traffic. No traffic is ever enough, when traffic stop growing, the income of the website stops as well. One of the best way increased traffic, sign ups or sales with no cost is using traffic exchange. <a href="http://javaongsan.github.com/recommends/trafficswarm/">TrafficSwarm</a> is one of the largest traffic exchange out there.</p>

<p><strong>What is <a href="http://javaongsan.github.com/recommends/trafficswarm/">TrafficSwarm</a></strong>
First of all What is traffic exchange? A traffic exchange basically allows members to trade views of their websites. Members join the program and earns credit by clicking on a advertisement that will lead to another website. When you accumulate enough credit, you will be able to put in an advertisement for your own website. <a href="http://javaongsan.github.com/recommends/trafficswarm/">TrafficSwarm</a> has been one my favorite and most effective traffic source. It is a bit different than others because it allows you to look at a group of classified ads first before clicking on the ones you want to see.</p>

<p><strong>Setting Up An Advertisement</strong>
To set up your advertisement, on the bottom of the page and you'll find Manage Your Site Promotions. This is where you add your own website URLs for others to see. You can select which category where your ads will appear.</p>

<p><strong>Earn More Credits</strong>
To accumulate more credits you need to surf other sites, each sites pays 1-5 credits randomly. You can also earn a 100 free credits when you refer new members.  As with all similar programs on the web there's a free version and a pro version.  To get optimum benefit it's recommended that you use the pro version.  If you want to earn more credits simply upgrade to Pro member which cost $30 a month. Pro member benefits include better ad display, more credits per clicks, etc.</p>

<p><strong>Income Results</strong>
Total number of visitors sent to my site on Dec 07: 104
Time spent to generate 100 credits perday: 30min
Total number sales: 2
Cost: $0 (I just upgraded to the Pro version for more traffic, but even the Pro version costs about a buck a day.)
Sale conversion rate: 2 in 104
Profit from TrafficSwarm: $54</p>

<p>The best part is that this program is actually worth the PRO upgrade. At $30 per month, in just one week, I make enough commissions to cover this cost.</p>

<p><strong>Advance Techniques</strong>
I used a rather straight forward approach in catching sales. I direct my <a href="http://javaongsan.github.com/recommends/trafficswarm/">TrafficSwarm</a> traffic to my sales page. However, an effective lead capturing method is to used a squeeze page to capture leads. A squeeze page consist of a free bonus which will be given to users when they fill up and submit the opt-in forms. The email list can then be used to promote different products, as the list gets bigger so does your profit.</p>

<p>If you need traffic to your website or your client's websites, try <a href="http://javaongsan.github.com/recommends/trafficswarm/">TrafficSwarm</a> today. Sign up for the Pro version if you are serious in a good traffic generator. New joiners are given with 100 free credits as  a bonus.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
