<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: web 2.0 | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/web-2-0/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Google Luanch OpenSocial]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/11/03/so-google-luanch-opensocial/"/>
    <updated>2007-11-03T05:24:18+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/11/03/so-google-luanch-opensocial</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You must have rad all the buzz about Google new toy <a href="http://code.google.com/apis/opensocial">OpenSocial</a>. OpenSocial is a set of common APIs that make it easy to create and host social applications on the web. OpenSocial allows developers to write an application once that will run anywhere that supports the OpenSocial APIs. Global members of the OpenSocial community include <a href="http://www.myspace.com/">MySpace</a>, <a href="http://www.engage.com/e/home.htm">Engage.com</a>, <a href="http://www.friendster.com/">Friendster</a>, <a href="http://www.hi5.com/">hi5</a>, <a href="http://www.hyves.net/">Hyves</a>, <a href="http://www.imeem.com/">imeem</a>, <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/">LinkedIn</a>, <a href="http://www.ning.com/">Ning</a>, <a href="http://www.oracle.com/index.html">Oracle</a>, <a href="https://www.google.com/accounts/ServiceLogin?service=orkut&amp;continue=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.orkut.com%2FRedirLogin.aspx%3Fmsg%3D0%26page%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.orkut.com%252F&amp;hl=en-US&amp;rm=false&amp;passive=true">orkut,</a> <a href="http://www.plaxo.com/info">Plaxo</a>, <a href="http://www.salesforce.com/">Salesforce.com</a>, <a href="http://www.sixapart.com/">Six Apart</a>, <a href="http://www.tianji.com/index.html">Tianji</a>, <a href="http://www.viadeo.com/en/connexion/">Viadeo</a>, and <a href="http://www.xing.com/">XING</a>.</p>

<p>The  problem  with social networking  development for independent developer is portability.  Every social networking site has its own APIs. When a application is developed for one social networking site, it is not compatible with another. With OpenSocial, that problem is solved.  In order for developers to get started immediately, Orkut has opened a limited sandbox that you can use to start building  apps using the OpenSocial APIs.</p>

<p>OpenSocial is built upon Google Gadget technology. With the Google Gadget Editor and a simple key/value API, you can build a complete social app with no server at all. Of course, you can also host your application on your own servers if you prefer. In all cases, Google's gadget caching technology can ease your bandwidth demands.</p>

<p>Review the <a href="http://code.google.com/apis/opensocial/docs/">OpenSocial API docs</a>. There are two ways to access the  OpenSocial API: client-side using the JavaScript API and server-side using RESTful data APIs. You can get some exposure by writing your first social gadget for <a href="http://code.google.com/apis/orkut/">Orkut</a>. Visit <a href="http://opensocialapis.blogspot.com">OpenSocial blog</a> for the latest news.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails, The Real Web 2.0 Programming Language]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/10/14/ruby-on-rails-the-real-web-20-programming-language/"/>
    <updated>2007-10-14T10:38:28+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/10/14/ruby-on-rails-the-real-web-20-programming-language</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://www.rubyonrails.org/images/rails.png" alt="Ruby On Rails" />Ruby on Rails is a free web application framework that aims to increase the speed and ease with which database-driven web sites can be created and offers skeleton code frameworks (scaffolding) from the outset. Ruby on Rails was created by David Heinemeier Hansson, a Danish.</p>

<p>Ruby on Rails is based on Ruby is a reflective, dynamic, object-oriented programming language. It combines syntax inspired by Perl with Smalltalk-like object-oriented features, and also shares some features with Python, Lisp, Dylan, and CLU. Ruby is a single-pass interpreted language. Its official implementation is free software written in C. The language was created by Yukihiro "Matz" Matsumoto, who started working on Ruby on February 24, 1993, and released it to the public in 1995. "Ruby" was named as a gemstone because of a joke within Matsumoto's circle of friends alluding to Perl's name</p>

<p>You are able to develop a web application <em>at least</em> ten times faster with Rails than you can with a typical Java framework. Rails takes full advantage of Ruby, which means you write fewer lines of code to implement your application. Keeping your code small means faster development and fewer bugs, which makes your code easier to understand, maintain, and enhance.</p>

<p>Ruby on Rails have the ability to generate ready to use codes based on your database, which is MySQL most of the time. As a complete framework, its already web 2.0 ready. Whats lacking right now is the hosting for ruby. Most hosting company do not offer Ruby on Rails. Ruby on Rails have more potential as a full web 2.0 than PHP. You can learn more about <a href="http://www.rubyonrails.org">Ruby on Rails here.
</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
