<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Blogging | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/blogging/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T11:35:11+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to know if you are ready for your niche]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/03/12/how-to-know-if-you-are-ready-for-your-niche/"/>
    <updated>2009-03-12T05:54:22+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/03/12/how-to-know-if-you-are-ready-for-your-niche</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Your gone through some steps or routine to come to a conclusion on your niche for your website, blog or article campaign. You are all set and passionate about your niche and ready to unleash it on the www audiences. Now before you do that and possible end up with a dead campaign or blog, do a simple test to make sure you are ready for it. Write 20 articles on your niche without any references material, simply using your own words and knowledge. Once your are done spin 5 sub articles out each of this 20 articles. If you are able to do that you have a year worth of content and probably more. Now for a little link muscle. Use 20 on your blog and each of the 5 spin article on a sub domain blog linking to its main. For article campaign simple submit 20 articles to 1 main article directory and separate the 5 across an other directory linking to the main article. Now you have something worthwhile to keep going.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking About Starting Another Blog?]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/05/04/thinking-about-starting-another-blog/"/>
    <updated>2008-05-04T03:50:15+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/05/04/thinking-about-starting-another-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Are you thinking of starting another blog? What are the some of the points to take note of? I have learned some important things about operating multiple blogs and websites since I started online.</p>

<p>Do you have time to start another blog?
How much spare time do you have? Many people have full-time jobs and work more than your average 40 hour per week. They have a family and commitments. Take some time to evaluate your life right now. Come up with a schedule of your life in blocks of 2 hours. block out your working hours and traveling time to work. Fill out your family time, meal time, entertainment time, workout time, blogging time and whatever is that you do. At the end of this exercise, you have clear idea of where all your time goes to. Find the block of time which are non productive like watching TV, reading newspaper or anything thats does not contribute to growing your income. All you need are 1 block of 2 hours a day.</p>

<p>Define blogging frequency and posting time before hand. When you start a second blog it might seem quick and easy to maintain, but it will only become more involved and time consuming over time. A discipline approach will help you go further. You may reevaluate your schedule every quarter and adjust your time slot accordingly.</p>

<p>Before you start a new blog, take some time and do a self evaluation. Only start enough blog that you have time for. The last thing you want is to start too many blogs and have to give up some of them.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can't make money blogging]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/06/you-cant-make-money-blogging/"/>
    <updated>2008-03-06T06:45:46+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/06/you-cant-make-money-blogging</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to popular believe, you can't make lots of money blogging. If you believe that writing a blog will eventually make you a six figure income and quick your job, this is going to hurt. I know you list all the six figure income bloggers and all your endless example to prove me   wrong. If you are one such blogger, I grantee your income is as low as your daily bus fare.</p>

<p>You don't make money blogging, you make money marketing your blog. Make Sense? Income from blogs comes from ad placement. To sell and ad you need to market your blog. No advertiser will know that you have a blog and that you are selling ad space. To promote your blog, you need to do it at forums, other blog, social networking sites and build up your brand. Then you need traffic and readers to boast your revenue, you can't get this by blogging. You get this done by doing  whole lot of other things.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prewritten blog post]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/05/prewritten-blog-post/"/>
    <updated>2008-03-05T06:26:48+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/05/prewritten-blog-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After a few month of blogging, you find that you are stuck and you need to blog constantly to keep your traffic, revenue and readers. What happens when you need to spent time with your family during weekends, work overtime on a new project or go away on a trip? The best way would be to write you post in advance, stock them up for rainy days.</p>

<p>I used different method to generate posts. When you finish a post, take sometime to write another post on the same topic retaining   most of the content, giving it a different twist. These posts can be recall in the future when you need something urgently. Write a series of post about 5 to 7 surrounding a particular topic. This post can be used on occasions when you are away for a few days.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know your reader]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/12/04/know-your-reader/"/>
    <updated>2007-12-04T03:29:54+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/12/04/know-your-reader</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>The importances of getting to know your reader</strong>
If you have ever tried blogging for money, you will be aware of the importance of choosing the right content for your target audience. Only when your giving your audience what they are looking for, they will will start to trust you and purchase some of the products that you are selling or promoting. To achieve this, you need know your audience, their interests, likes and dislikes. Know your audience and their needs, use this knowledge to help design your blog and write your posts.</p>

<p><strong>Who is your target reader?</strong>
To get to know your readers better, you can start to profile your readers. Set up Google Analytics, Mybloglog, look at comments, email them and study and come up with a way to identified and categories them. You can define such characteristics such as spending power, age, interest etc. With a target reader profile you should find it easier to generate the content that will appeal to them.</p>

<p>When you know what the audience wants and likes, when you know your audience, they become more interested in what you have to say. Often the blogger does not even have to be a good writer, but if the audience feels there is good communication, they will listen and enjoy the post. Knowing the audience can result in the benefits you want.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
