<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: gadget | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/gadget/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web-Based Kindle Cloud Reader]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/08/10/web-based-kindle-cloud-reader/"/>
    <updated>2011-08-10T08:20:37+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/08/10/web-based-kindle-cloud-reader</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Kindle apps for iPad is not available in a lot of countries like Singapore. The only way to get one is to sign in an US based iTunes account. Now there,s a cloud reader which is accessible any where via https://read.amazon.com.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kindle Available For Sale Outside US]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/10/12/kindle-available-for-sale-outside-us/"/>
    <updated>2009-10-12T15:17:39+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/10/12/kindle-available-for-sale-outside-us</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Finally...we get Kindle ship to us outside of US. Amazon introduces a new addition to the Kindle family of wireless reading devices: <strong>Kindle with U.S. and International Wireless</strong>. With this new Kindle, you can receive your books, newspapers, and magazines wirelessly while at home or abroad in over 100 countries. Whether you're in New York, Paris, São Paulo, Mumbai, Beijing, Tokyo, or Sydney, you can think of a book and be reading it in less than 60 seconds. The $279 Kindle with U.S. and International Wireless can be preordered today for delivery starting in two weeks.</p>

<p>Kindle utilizes the same 3G wireless technology as advanced cell phones, so you never need to hunt for a Wi-Fi hotspot. Unlike cell phones, there are no monthly wireless bills and no yearly contracts. There is no software to install, and no syncing required.</p>

<p>The 8" x 5.3" x 0.36" Kindle is as thin as most magazines and weighs less than a paperback—but can hold 1,500 books. Its electronic-ink screen looks and reads like real paper with no glare—even in bright sunlight. A long battery life means you can read for up to two weeks on a single charge.</p>

<p>You can order one <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00154JDAI?tag=YOUR_ID_HERE-20%20and%20http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0015T963C?tag=wizcoder-20"> here</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
