<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: blog | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T11:35:11+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yahoo mail release old deactivated email address]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/07/15/yahoo-mail-release-old-deactivated-email-address/"/>
    <updated>2011-07-15T06:50:44+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/07/15/yahoo-mail-release-old-deactivated-email-address</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Not sure how long it's has been going on but Yahoo Mail release the lock on old deactivated email address. If you have ever deactivated an account with yahoo because of spam or whatever reason, you can register for the same username which is not possible last time.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grub rescue error]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/03/14/grub-rescue-error/"/>
    <updated>2011-03-14T02:14:21+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/03/14/grub-rescue-error</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I used gpart to partition a 600g hard disk with preinstall win7. When I boot up after that, boot sector for win7 was gone or maybe replaced. The grup rescue command prompt appear. I couldn't fix it.
I simply install Linux and got a new boot menu.</p>

<p>When I migrate win7 to virtual box the same problem appear. This time I had to use win7 rescues disk to fix the problem. Below are the steps I found</p>

<ol>
<li>Put the Windows Vista installation disc in the disc drive, and then start the computer.</li>
<li>Press a key when you are prompted.</li>
<li>Select a language, a time, a currency, a keyboard or an input method, and then click Next.</li>
<li>Click Repair your computer.</li>
<li>Click the operating system that you want to repair, and then click Next.</li>
<li>In the System Recovery Options dialog box, click Command Prompt.</li>
<li>Type Bootrec.exe /FixMbr, and then press ENTER.</li>
</ol>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[DVD Player Region Hack]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/02/05/dvd-player-region-hack/"/>
    <updated>2011-02-05T02:54:22+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2011/02/05/dvd-player-region-hack</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I purchase a LG dvd player sometime ago. It was a display set on sale $300 for a $500 set. Recently, it somehow cold booted, and some DVD I bought cannot be played. A message "Wrong regional code".</p>

<p>I google a bit and found that I could hack the region code.</p>

<p>I got the instruction from videohelp.com/dvdhacks
1. Press "Home key on Remote Control</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Using your cursor keys, move to "Setup" and press "Enter" on the RCU</p></li>
<li><p>Move cursor to "Lock" icon using down arrow on Remote Control</p></li>
<li><p>Press "Zero(0)" key on Remote Control 7 times (0-0-0-0-0-0-0)</p></li>
</ol>


<p>A dialogue box with a message saying "Congratulations! Region Change Fee!"</p>

<p>I suspect my set was set to region free by the sales guys at the store when on display.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating multiple streams of income online]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/02/24/generating-multiple-streams-of-income-online/"/>
    <updated>2008-02-24T05:07:49+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/02/24/generating-multiple-streams-of-income-online</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Do you have only one website thats is bringing the cash now? Do you find it hard to increase the income from that site? If so, it may be time to set up another site theres complete different from what you are doing. Lets look at the types of sites we can set up.</p>

<p>Forum
Forum are the best source of passive income online, they require minimum management and most of the information are user contributed. The toughest thing about starting a forum is getting users to sign up and generate interesting topics. Revenue comes from private ad placement and ad networks.</p>

<p>Blog
Blog are the simplest to start. You write whatever you want. It the easy to get traffic. Revenue comes from a wide variety and is the most versatile of all.</p>

<p>Auto Blog
Its a blog that updates it self. A very effective way to make instant income but die as soon as it start making good profits.</p>

<p>Scripted Sites
Scripted Sites like myspace resources sites requires no maintainences makes primary income from Adsense. This site requires you to promote the site at the beginning.</p>

<p>These are some of the sites I have been playing with now. Whats are the type of sites you own?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to be a successful entrepreneur]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/02/19/how-to-be-a-successful-entrepreneur/"/>
    <updated>2008-02-19T04:03:40+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/02/19/how-to-be-a-successful-entrepreneur</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wikipedia describe entrepreneur as An entrepreneur is a person who operates a new enterprise or venture and assumes some accountability for the inherent risks. If you have line up all the successful entrepreneur in the world and tried to profile them, you find that they all different. From the size, looks, to the way they think and operate. There are no fixed rule to become an entrepreneur, but at some point you be required to take risks or perform and work in a way that most peers will not. If you go back to all the successful entrepreneurs and ask them for the key to their success, you probably get as many as the number of people you asked. How do become successful? We do it by failing more than others and we get up each time. Technical skills like marketing, writing business plan, managing can be learn but attitude and commitment are forged through countless hardship, visualization, developing passion and undying attitude. What the most important thing you can do to be a successful entrepreneur is simply "Don't Quit"</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
