<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: rss | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/rss/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T11:35:11+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you subscribe?]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/02/02/do-you-subscribe/"/>
    <updated>2008-02-02T07:37:24+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/02/02/do-you-subscribe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The actual question is What are your criteria for subscribing to a particular RSS feed? Feed count, popularity or simply because you like it? What ever your reason, you shouldn't have a criteria. In fact, my suggestion is to subscribe to any blog you came across. like anyone else I don't like to help a blog increased their feed count or readership by subscribing to them, especially when there are only 1 digit. I do not subscribe to any blog who I am not found of, or if I think they are boring, or for whatever reason. Since reading a post y John Chow about his idea of tracking a numerous blogs for ideas, I started to wonder. Could I be missing out on some valuable informations by refusing to subscribe to a blog? I think the answer is obvious. Now that I amÂ   writingÂ   more blog, I need more informations,Â   someÂ   in specific niche, I found that its really useful to read more blogs. Not only does it generate new ideas for content, some of them have good writing styles which I can follow. I may also be tracking blogs that are starting out and testing certain techniques on blogging or affiliate marketing. There a lot of things that I learn through other people's experiences.</p>

<p>Many will argue the time I wasted tracking so many feeds, well I not going for PHD here so I don't study every single content in details, I simple do a quick scan of all the titles and pick out a few that I will go through. You may also used different readers, or create different foldersÂ   to separate the feeds. A golden rule that I live by now "Only Subscribe, Do Not Unsubscribe!".</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
