<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Making Money From Blogging | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/making-money-from-blogging/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to increase link sales and paid post pricing.]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/10/how-to-increase-link-sales-and-paid-post-pricing/"/>
    <updated>2008-03-10T10:09:48+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/03/10/how-to-increase-link-sales-and-paid-post-pricing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Most average blogger will scout around paid-post or link sales networks and pick up scrapes. $5 for a blog post or $3 for a link on your blog. Have you wonder how other blog get $100 dollars or more for a link or paid post? Are you pasting link all over your blog and not making enough for a decent meal at Macdonald's?</p>

<p>I got few pointers for you guys if you are looking to improve your pricing.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Set a monthly target on how much you need.
You need to know how much you need so you know when to stop. Set a reasonable target. If your link is price at$5 don't set a target of $1000 link sales. A more appropriates target is $50.</p></li>
<li><p>Use common sense quality control.
Accept only relevant advertisements to your sites. This makes the links more acceptable to  your users and increase click through which result in returning customer.</p></li>
<li><p>Do not sell more than a month.
A very common mistake that I see regularly is selling permanent links. Its like having a scare on your face. This will only limit your income potential.</p></li>
<li><p>PR and traffic is important too.
Link price are pretty much tie to traffic and PR so make sure you spent enough time on both of them. As your traffic and PR increases you can adjust your price accordingly but when they drop do not drop your link price. If you do, you are back to square 1.</p></li>
<li><p>Don't depend on Advertiser networks to sell your links, ad space or paid post. Email site owners, go to forum, do whatever it takes to make the sales. You are the sales director of your blog, you are in charge of selling, don't wait for someone else to do it for you.</p></li>
</ol>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many blog can you write on?]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/30/how-many-blog-can-you-write-on/"/>
    <updated>2008-01-30T08:19:31+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/30/how-many-blog-can-you-write-on</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There are lots of debate on the number of blog one should have. Most successful bloggers are likely to write only one blog and it seems like you only need one blog to be profitable. What happens when your blog did not take off? Maybe there are no readers, not enough traffic, or simply a bad niche? I do believe that if you work hard on one blog alone, you eventually get there, but what about when you have not make it yet. Your blog have too little traffic or readers to sell advertisement and your Adsense earning is only a few cents for entire month.</p>

<p>When I started, I started 5 blogs and only kept 2. Overtime I have started new blogs, keep some going and shutdown some. I was working on a full-time job back then, I still found time to work each blog daily. There are many benefits of starting multiple blogs. You have a sharper learning curve, you save time by experimenting different things on different blogs. After a period of time, you will shutdown the less preforming ones and work on the better performing ones. You choose to let this discarded blog float, where you might find some use for them in the future or use it to link to some of your websites, you might even be able to sell links or advertising spaces on them.</p>

<p>While most of my blog were started with free host, I have found that time and time again that if you host your own blog, you get better traffic fast. I have one blog lunch that will gain organic traffic the next day. Of course there a lot more SEO tactics involved but then again you can't use them on free hosts like blogger.</p>

<p>I doÂ   recommend you start as many blogs as you can, even 1 a day is not too much. Start them on a good domain name. Pack them with contents,Â   try to write as many post as possible till you run dry of content before your lunch. Always have a sitemap and submit them to the search engines. Always have some kind of tracking code like Google analytics where you are to track keywords and popular post. Once you get a couple of blog, you can make money by doing paid posts, selling links or ad space, or you can sell the entire blog.</p>

<p>Just in case you are wondering I run 7 blogs now. Its definitely more profitable than when I am running one.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[October Earnings]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/11/01/october-earnings/"/>
    <updated>2007-11-01T15:32:14+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2007/11/01/october-earnings</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How's your earning this month? October is a good month for me, I have my earning rebounded from $0 back to $166 plus. This month, I am not solely rely on blogging. I have expanded to other areas of making money. There also a lot more opportunities now that I have 3 sites with PRs. I should rewrite my list of money makers and make it more comprehensive. This guide will probably help a few people get up to $100 a month if they have not make money online before.</p>

<p>I have decided to put up as many sites to diversified my incomes. Many eggs in many baskets. The idea is to make money from multiple websites, all with residual incomes by creating websites that are self maintenance or needs very little maintenance needed. This month, I am exploring more area technically which is my strength rather than writing and marketing. I have now own a VPS which makes it easier for me to run scripts and host as many website. The cost is higher in October because of the VPS and a few expired domains. It will be good for this new site to support itself soon.</p>

<p>The coming month, you see less of my post. I have plan a couple of important onces like my research and result from leaving high PR comments, the list of money maker I mentioned and possibly a guide on setting up and using a VPS. This is all I can think of right now. It is going to be a busy  month a head.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
