<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: SEO | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/seo/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Articles Can Bring Your Blog More Traffic]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/04/articles-can-bring-your-blog-more-traffic/"/>
    <updated>2008-01-04T06:11:37+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/04/articles-can-bring-your-blog-more-traffic</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Did you know you can add articles from other source to your blog to help draw traffic to it? By adding good quality content to your blog, not only can you perform better in organic traffic, you can attract more readers to your site faster. Yes, we are talking about finding keyword articles to boast our traffics.</p>

<p>These keywords can improve the volume and quality of traffic to a web site from search engines via "natural" ("organic" or "algorithmic") search results. Usually, the higher a site is presented in the search results, the more searchers will visit that site. To scrape articles is easy, you can use free content from article directory, hire a writer, or get it from other blogs. All you need is to give credits to the original author. I suggest you scrape about 30 articles in one go and spread them out in your archives, that means creating this content in past dates. To get index fast you need to submit your new sitemap to <a href="http://www.google.com/webmasters/">Google Webmaster Central.</a></p>

<p>You be seeing some exciting traffic pretty soon, if you get your keywords right, you can get about 50-100 unique organic traffic per day.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
