<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: affiliate marketing | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/affiliate-marketing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T10:31:36+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clickbank direct deposit]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/03/14/clickbank-direct-deposit/"/>
    <updated>2009-03-14T03:00:10+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/03/14/clickbank-direct-deposit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Clickbank direct deposit is really great I got my paid out for March in 2 days and none of that expensive clearing fee. Comparing to my feburary cheaque payment, I receive it by mail last week and its still processing. I enjoying the shorter turn arond as now I have more funds to paly with. My latest paid out is about $600.  </p>

<p>The latest news from Clickbank, Now they do not allowing P2P products anymore. That means no more movies, music, PSP, iPod, Satellite TV for PC, Wii products.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Landing page]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/01/18/landing-page/"/>
    <updated>2009-01-18T09:44:31+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/01/18/landing-page</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Building a landing page can be very confusing. I have studied many landing page website recently, and found that these model works really well.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Use attractive pictures to attract more users to research the title.</p></li>
<li><p>Analysis of potential customers pain and problems with the current services or product.</p></li>
<li><p>sell the benefits of product or service not the features.</p></li>
<li><p>Using a large number testimonials.</p></li>
<li><p>Money back guarantee.</p></li>
<li><p>Give additional benefits for customers who make immediately purchase.</p></li>
<li><p>Build an opt-in list, its takes 7 follow up to make a sale.</p></li>
</ol>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Keyword Tool updated]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/07/09/google-keyword-tool-updated/"/>
    <updated>2008-07-09T14:34:18+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/07/09/google-keyword-tool-updated</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://bp0.blogger.com/_27oPxt14mJc/SHRRKJgiIOI/AAAAAAAAABY/k458aACLN0Q/s400/keywordtool.gif" alt="" />
Now, when you use the Keyword Tool to search for relevant keywords to include in your keyword list, you'll be able to see the approximate number of search queries matching your keywords that were performed on Google and the search network, instead of the graphic bar.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clickbank test exceeds $100]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/07/02/clickbank-test-exceeds-100/"/>
    <updated>2008-07-02T13:48:01+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/07/02/clickbank-test-exceeds-100</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As of 1st of July my experiment with <a href="http://javaongsan.github.com/2008/06/11/google-adwords/">google cash concept</a> exceeds $100. I am runnning one campaign, one keyword with 2 ads and one product. I will continue to the experience with a landing page and see how it goes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clickbank finally offers Direct Deposit]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/07/01/clickbank-finally-offers-direct-deposit/"/>
    <updated>2008-07-01T13:02:29+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/07/01/clickbank-finally-offers-direct-deposit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Clickbanks finally offers Driect Deposit but wait you have to meet all the requirements. To be eligible, an account must have first received three paper paychecks within any 90-day period. Additionally, only accounts in the following countries are eligible at this time: Australia, Austria, Belgium, Canada, France, Germany, Ireland, Mexico, The Netherlands, New Zealand, Spain, Switzerland, United Kingdom, United States. Dam!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
