<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: affiliate marketing | Ong Swee San]]></title>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/categories/affiliate-marketing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-23T11:35:11+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clickbank direct deposit]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/03/14/clickbank-direct-deposit/"/>
    <updated>2009-03-14T03:00:10+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2009/03/14/clickbank-direct-deposit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Clickbank direct deposit is really great I got my paid out for March in 2 days and none of that expensive clearing fee. Comparing to my feburary cheaque payment, I receive it by mail last week and its still processing. I enjoying the shorter turn arond as now I have more funds to paly with. My latest paid out is about $600.  </p>

<p>The latest news from Clickbank, Now they do not allowing P2P products anymore. That means no more movies, music, PSP, iPod, Satellite TV for PC, Wii products.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Mistake with ClickBank]]></title>
    <link href="http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/20/big-mistake-with-clickbank/"/>
    <updated>2008-01-20T04:49:25+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://javaongsan.github.com/blog/2008/01/20/big-mistake-with-clickbank</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>"Boy, you got to pay attention to details!". I just read the clickbank FAQ, I guess I am the last person on planet earth who missed this. I put all my clickbank affiliate links on iframe. If you don't not what I taking about read the 2 clause below.</p>

<p><em><strong>10. Will I get referral credit if I hide hoplinks by making them open into a frame, iframe, layer, applet, image, or other sub-window object?</strong></em></p>

<p><em>No. These are illegal hoplinks. For security reasons, and to ensure proper tracking of your referrals, all hoplinks must be targeted to the top level of a new or existing window.</em></p>

<p><em><strong>11. What happens if I do make illegal hoplinks?</strong></em></p>

<p><em>The short answer is that if you make illegal hoplinks you will lose money.</em></p>

<p><em>Hoplinks targeted to frames or iframes are automatically retargeted to fill the top level of same window, with full affiliate referral credit awarded. Note that this retargeting may have the unintended effect of displacing your entire web site.</em></p>

<p><em>Hoplinks targeted to images or other invisible html objects give you no affilate referral credit at all. In some cases they will also prevent you from receiving affiliate referral credit for legal hoplinks on the same page.</em></p>

<p><em>Accounts that are found to be abusing the hoplink system may be terminated without notice.</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
